articleunderground.com 2016-03-15

# Article Underground Privacy Policy

[Article Underground](http://www.articleunderground.com/) Navigation: [Members Only](http://www.articleunderground.com/members.html) \- [Article Marketplace](http://www.articleunderground.com/marketplace/) \- [Affiliate Programs](http://www.articleunderground.com/affiliate-programs/) \- [Article Blog](http://articleblog.articleunderground.com/) \- [Content & Traffic System](http://www.articleunderground.com/content-traffic.html) \- [Bonuses](http://www.articleunderground.com/bonuses.html) \- [Article Packs](http://www.articleunderground.com/article-packs/) \- [Public Article Directory](http://www.articleunderground.com/directory/) \- [Special Reports](http://www.articleunderground.com/special-reports/) \- [Multimedia](http://www.articleunderground.com/multimedia/) \- Free Content \- [Keyword Density Analyzer Tool](http://www.articleunderground.com/webmaster/keyword-density-tool.html) \- [Article Marketing](http://www.articleunderground.com/article-marketing/) \- [Announce Your Articles](http://www.articleunderground.com/announce-articles/) \- [Keyword Research](http://www.articleunderground.com/keyword-research/) \- [Article Samples](http://www.articleunderground.com/article-samples.html) \- [Terms and Conditions](http://www.articleunderground.com/terms_and_conditions.html) \- [Earnings Disclaimer](http://www.articleunderground.com/earnings_disclaimer.html) \- [Privacy Policy](http://www.articleunderground.com/privacy_policy.html) \- [Who Are These Guys?](http://www.articleunderground.com/who-we-be.html) \- [Webmaster](http://www.articleunderground.com/webmaster/) \- [Support](http://www.articleunderground.com/support-free.html)

**Privacy Policy** ****

Updated 6-15-2010

My name is Mike Liebner of ArticleUnderground.com which is owned and operated by my company Creative Power of Studio City, California. This is our Privacy Policy.

Your privacy and security are very important to us. We appreciate the subscribers, members and visitors who visit this web site and understand the value of protecting your rights. We want you to be able to enjoy our information and services with complete confidence that your privacy and safety will be our highest concern.

There are 3 classes of individuals whom services and information is provided to which will be outlined in this document.

1) Members - Members buy a product or service and pay a fee for access to information. We do not directly collect your financial information, but rather employ the use of a 3rd party collection service such as PayPal whom is liable through their terms and services which you have agreed to if you have made a purchase. Your name and email address and any other information you may provide to us is strictly for use in house and is not shared with any company or individuals. This information is secure and protected so you can become a member in confidence that you will be safe from public disclosure. This information is stored in a secure database, and is only available to individuals with proper clearance. Members can cancel future payments by visiting the vendor that collected their subscription fee - ie PayPal and/or other service. 3rd party regulations may apply. 

2) Subscribers - Subscribers opt-in and verify that they desire to have access to information provided on this web site and through emails and other communications. We employ the use of a 3rd party Autoresponder service Aweber whom is responsible for collecting and protecting your information. Your name and email address and any other information you may provide to us is strictly for use in house and is not shared with any company or individuals. This information is secure and protected so you can become a subscriber in confidence that you will be safe from public disclosure. This information is stored in a secure database, and is only available to individuals with proper clearance. Subscribers can opt-out of receiving future communications from us when you set up your account or by updating your account information.

3) Visitor - Visitors are not required to provide any information nor is any collected from you or your computer. 

ArticleUnderground.com contracts with third party service partners to provide us with data collection, storage and reporting services. Under no circumstances are these partners permitted to use your information in any manner, other than to help us make our site more useful for our visitors. 

Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data file transferred by a Web site to your computer's hard drive. We may send cookies when you view our web pages, make purchases, request information, or register yourself for certain services. Accepting the cookies used on our site does not give us access to your Personally Identifiable Information, but we may use the cookies to identify your computer for enhanced features.

Third party vendors, including Google may show ads on sites on the internet. 

Third party vendors, including Google may use cookies to serve ads based on prior visits to this website. 

Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

ArticleUndergound.com does contain links to other sites. ArticleUndergound.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy please refer them to the conatct as listed below. 

Mike Liebner  
ArticleUnderground.com  
Creative Power   
12400 Ventura Blvd. #207  
Studio City, CA 91604  
(310) 734-1574 

Questions??? email: [articles@articleunderground.com](mailto:articles@articleunderground.com)

Article Underground is a member of the [HQ Ads Net](http://www.hqtextads.com/)
